Tomas Gonzalez User Experience Designer

tomasjgonzalez.com admin@tomasjgonzalez.com linkedin.com/in/tomasjgo +64 027 397 8220 Cockle Bay, Auckland

Summary

User Experience Designer with 5+ years of experience. I have a passion to solve problems by creating data-driven and creative solutions. My role as a UX designer is about using design as a positive force, creating a more inclusive, efficient, and ethical digital world. More about me.

Employment History

Buildhub | User Experience Designer

2021-2024

- Designed the brand strategy, logo and website.
- Designed and maintained a comprehensive recruitment & onboarding system to successfully attract more than +2900 overseas applicants.
- Worked with a developer to create an ATS (Applicant Tracking System) + Operational system for the company, to help recruit, hire, and onboard candidates.
- Stakeholder management and working within a multi-disciplinary team.

Synergy Advisory | UX / UI Designer

2018 - 2021

- Established first design guide and asset library. Designed brand strategy, logo and website.
- Setting up a comprehensive E-com site for start-up(s) with Shopify, research and design of content and successfully helped increased conversion rates.
- Interactive workshop planning and facilitation. 'Business Growth & Design workshops."

Freelance Work | UX / UI Designer

2017 - Ongoing

Work primarily consisted of web projects and logo designs: Wireframing, UI design, website creation with CMS' (WIX). Designing print and branding assets (content patterns, video/social media content).

Skills

Software: Figma, Illustrator, InDesign, Premiere Pro, Google Suite, Microsoft Office, WIX, Shopify, Keynote.

Visual: User Interface design, Graphic & Identity design, Visual design, HTML / CSS (SASS)

Process: UX Writing, Prototyping, Low-High Fidelity Wireframing, User Research & Testing, Accessibility.

Soft Skills: Curiosity & continuous learning, Communication skills, Open mindedness, Attention to detail.

Spoken Languages: English (*fluent*), Spanish (*fluent*).

Professional affiliations

Abroad Global Charitable Trust (Trustee)

2021 - 2023

Social Programs: Holistic English, Textile Waste Initiative. See portfolio for more.

Education

Auckland University of Technology — AUT

Feb 2015 - Dec 2018

Bachelor of Creative Technologies

Interaction Design Foundation — IDF

Mar 2018 - Mar 2019

Certificate in Gestalt Psychology and Web Design & Accessibility: "How do Design for All"

References on request.